spicytec.com 2012-12-15

# Spicytec: Policy

**The  <http://www.spicytec.com/> Privacy Statement**

What follows is the Privacy Statement for all <http://www.spicytec.com/> websites (blogs) including all the websites run under the <http://www.spicytec.com/> domain.

Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our [contact form](http://www.spicytec.com/p/contact-us.html).

**Email Addresses**

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share your email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We don’t currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

**Ownership of Information**

We aspire to do the right, ethical and legal thing in bringing you this site, and we ask that you use the same judgment as you read, use, link to, and share the content hosted on Spicytec. When utilizing Spicytec content, we ask that you give credit where appropriate and don’t edit our content – or content that belongs to others without permission.

We might have shown some of the contents shred at other blogs similar to spicytec.com. We are always giving the credit to the appropriate owner. So, if your copying our contents, please mention the other sites where these information obtained.  

We may have edited the first image of the post to fit to our template. But, All other contents are not edited and its original. If you see your design or work is edited and you don't like to see the edited contents, feel free to drop a message through our contact form.

**Comments/Message Boards**

Most [http://www.spicytec.com/](http://www.tuvie.com/) websites contain comment sections. We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. We have activated comment moderation for all the comments before publishing. Any comments you feel that is inappropriate, you can always drop a message to us.

**Third Party Cookies**

 About Google as Third Party Vendor  
\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
\- Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Traffic Reports**

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Legal proceedings**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but [http://www.spicytec.com](http://www.spicytec.com/) may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**

If <http://www.spicytec.com/> is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Links**

<http://www.spicytec.com/> website frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by <http://www.spicytec.com/>

**Notification of Changes**

When <http://www.spicytec.com/> makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
